    <TEXT>
        <Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_PORT_ROYAL_TRADE_QUEST_START</Tag>
        <English>We will fulfill the orders of his Majesty!</English>
        <German>Wir werden den Befehl Seiner Majestät erfüllen!</German>
    </TEXT>
    <TEXT>
        <Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_PORT_ROYAL_TRADE_QUEST_DONE</Tag>
        <English>For the glory and wealth of the motherland!</English>
        <German>Für Ruhm und Reichtum des Heimatlandes!</German>
    </TEXT>
    <TEXT>
        <Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_PORT_ROYAL_TRADE_QUEST_DONE_COLONIES</Tag>
        <English>For the Glory and Wealth of our colonies! Higher sale prices are always welcome!</English>
        <German>Für Ruhm und Reichtum unserer Kolonien! Höhere Verkaufspreise sind immer willkommen!</German>
    </TEXT>
    <TEXT>
        <Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_PORT_ROYAL_TRADE_QUEST_DONE1_COLONIES</Tag>
        <English>For the glory and wealth of our colonies! Let the smuggling with Port Royal flourish!</English>
        <German>Für Ruhm und Reichtum unserer Kolonien! Möge der Schmuggel mit Port Royal erblühen!</German>
    </TEXT>
    <TEXT>
        <Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_PORT_ROYAL_TRADE_QUEST_DONE2_COLONIES</Tag>
        <English>For the glory and wealth of our colonies! Death and destruction to foreign merchant fleets!</English>
        <German>Für Ruhm und Reichtum unserer Kolonien! Tod und verderben den fremden Handelsflotten!</German>
    </TEXT>
    <TEXT>
        <Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_PORT_ROYAL_TRADE_QUEST_DONE3_COLONIES</Tag>
        <English>For the glory and wealth of our colonies! Let's sink the enemy fleets!</English>
        <German>Für Ruhm und Reichtum unserer Kolonien! Lasst uns die gegnerischen Flotten versenken!</German>

    </TEXT>
    <TEXT>
        <Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_PORT_ROYAL_TRADE_QUEST_DONE4_COLONIES</Tag>
        <English>For the glory and wealth of our colonies! Hopefully the mercenaries will not turn against us!</English>
        <German>Für Ruhm und Reichtum unserer Kolonien! Hoffentlich wenden sich die Söldner nicht gegen uns!</German>
    </TEXT>
    <TEXT>
        <Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_PORT_ROYAL_TRADE_QUEST_DONE5_COLONIES</Tag>
        <English>For the glory and wealth of our colonies! Let the natives do the dirty work!</English>
        <German>Für Ruhm und Reichtum unserer Kolonien! Lasst die Ureinwohner die schmutzige Arbeit erledigen!</German>
    </TEXT>

    <TEXT>
        <Tag>TXT_KEY_WORLD_EVENTTRIGGER_PORT_ROYAL_TRADE_QUEST_BLADES_START</Tag>
        <English>The race to dominate the market in the colonies for [COLOR_FONT_GOLD]bladed weapons[COLOR_REVERT] from Port Royal has begun.</English>
        <German>Das Rennen zur Beherrschung des Marktes in den Kolonien für [COLOR_FONT_GOLD]Klingenwaffen[COLOR_REVERT] aus Port Royal hat begonnen.</German>
    </TEXT>
    <TEXT>
        <Tag>TXT_KEY_WORLD_EVENTTRIGGER_PORT_ROYAL_TRADE_QUEST_BLADES_DONE</Tag>
        <English>We have managed to become the dominant leader in the trade of [COLOR_FONT_GOLD]bladed weapons[COLOR_REVERT] from Port Royal.</English>
        <German>Uns ist es gelungen der dominante Marktführer für den Handel mit [COLOR_FONT_GOLD]Klingenwaffen[COLOR_REVERT] aus Port Royal zu werden.</German>
    </TEXT>
    <TEXT>
        <Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_TRIGGER_PORT_ROYAL_TRADE_QUEST_BLADES_START</Tag>
        <English>Our colonists are thrilled with the first shipments of [COLOR_FONT_GOLD]bladed weapons[COLOR_REVERT] from Port Royal. The governor of Port Royal asks us to become the dominant market leader.</English>
        <German>Die Bürger unserer Kolonien sind von den ersten Lieferungen von [COLOR_FONT_GOLD]Klingenwaffen[COLOR_REVERT] aus Port Royal begeistert. Der Gouverneur von Port Royal fordert uns auf der Dominante Marktführer zu werden.</German>
    </TEXT>
    <TEXT>
        <Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_PORT_ROYAL_TRADE_QUEST_BLADES_FAILED</Tag>
        <English>Another colonial power first succeeded in cornering the market in the colonies for [COLOR_FONT_GOLD]bladed weapons[COLOR_REVERT] from Port Royal.</English>
        <German>Einer anderen Kolonialmacht ist es zuerst gelungen den Markt in den Kolonien für [COLOR_FONT_GOLD]Klingenwaffen[COLOR_REVERT] aus Port Royal zu beherrschen.</German>
    </TEXT>
    <TEXT>
        <Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_TRIGGER_PORT_ROYAL_TRADE_QUEST_BLADES_DONE</Tag>
        <English>We have managed to become the dominant leader in the trade of [COLOR_FONT_GOLD]bladed weapons[COLOR_REVERT] from Port Royal. The governor of Port Royal is extremely satisfied.</English>
        <German>Uns ist es gelungen der dominante Marktführer für den Handel mit [COLOR_FONT_GOLD]Klingenwaffen[COLOR_REVERT] aus Port Royal zu werden. Der Gouverneur von Port Royal ist äusserst zufrieden.</German>
    </TEXT>
